Guide to the Department of Epidemiology and Public Health, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Departmental Files, 1940-1960; Series I
  - 1949-1950
    - Connecticut, State, of:
      - Commission on State Government Organization, 1949-1950 (Box 73, Folder 785-786)
      - Commission on State Government Organization, 1949-1950 (Box 74, Folder 787-789)
      - Department of Finance and Control, 1949-1950 (Box 74, Folder 790)
    - Connecticut State Medical Society, 1949-1950 (Box 74, Folder 791)
      - Academy of Pediatrics - State Study Committee (Root); Material on Final Report, 1949-1950 (Box 74, Folder 792)
    - Institute of Inter-American Affairs, 1949-1950 (Box 75, Folder 793)
    - Hawaii, 1949-1950 (Box 75, Folder 794)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1949-1950 (Box 75, Folder 797)
    - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1949-1950 (Box 75, Folder 798)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1949-1950 (Box 75, Folder 799-801)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis: New Haven Chapter, 1949-1950 (Box 76, Folder 802)
    - National Health Council, 1949-1950 (Box 76, Folder 803-805)
      - National Social Welfare Assembly, 1949-1950 (Box 76, Folder 806)
      - National Social Welfare Assembly, 1949-1950 (Box 77, Folder 807)
      - National Publicity Council, 1949-1950 (Box 77, Folder 808)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, 1949-1950 (Box 77, Folder 809-812)
      - Connecticut Public Health Nursing Association, 1949-1950 (Box 77, Folder 813)
    - National Research Council, 1949-1950 (Box 77, Folder 814)
    - National Sanitation Foundation, 1949-1950 (Box 78, Folder 815)
    - National society for the Prevention of Blindness, 1949-1950 (Box 78, Folder 816-819)
    - National Tuberculosis Association, 1949-1950 (Box 79, Folder 820-821)
      - Connecticut Tuberculosis Association, 1949-1950 (Box 79, Folder 822)
      - New Haven Tuberculosis Association (E.T.R.A.), 1949-1950 (Box 79, Folder 823)
      - Planning Committee, Third National Conference on College Health, 1949-1950 (Box 79, Folder 824)
    - New Haven Board of Health, 1949-1950 (Box 79, Folder 825-826)
      - minutes of meetings, 1949-1950 (Box 79, Folder 827)
      - Health Education Committee, 1949-1950 (Box 79, Folder 828)
      - Rheumatic Fever & Cardiac Program, 1949-1950 (Box 80, Folder 829)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies, 1949-1950 (Box 80, Folder 830)
    - New Haven Hospital: Grace-New Haven Community Hospital Building Fund, 1949-1950 (Box 80, Folder 831)
    - New Haven School Survey, 1949-1950 (Box 80, Folder 832)
    - New Haven Visiting Nurse Association, 1949-1950 (Box 80, Folder 833-834)
    - Rockefeller Foudation, 1949-1950 (Box 80, Folder 835)
    - Society of American Bacteriologists, 1949-1950 (Box 80, Folder 836)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1949-1950 (Box 81, Folder 837-838)
    - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration, 1949-1950 (Box 81, Folder 839)
    - United States Army, 1949-1950 (Box 81, Folder 840-842)
    - United States Army, 1949-1950 (Box 82, Folder 843)
    - United States Public Health Service, 1949-1950 (Box 82, Folder 844-846)
      - venereal disease study, 1949-1950 (Box 82, Folder 847)
      - mental hygiene, 1949-1950 (Box 82, Folder 848)
      - National Institutes of Health, 1949-1950 (Box 82, Folder 849)
      - Division of Medical and Hospital Resources, 1949-1950 (Box 82, Folder 850)
      - Division of Chronic Disease, 1949-1950 (Box 82, Folder 851)
    - Health Departments (City, County, State), 1949-1950 (Box 82, Folder 852)
      - Mississippi State Board of Health, 1949-1950 (Box 82, Folder 853)
    - World Health Organization, 1949-1950 (Box 82, Folder 854)
  - 1950-1951
    - General A, 1950-1951 (Box 83, Folder 855-857)
    - American Cancer Society, 1950-1951 (Box 83, Folder 858)
    - General B, 1950-1951 (Box 83, Folder 859)
    - A.S. Barnes & Company, 1950-1951 (Box 83, Folder 860-861)
    - General C, 1950-1951 (Box 84, Folder 862-863)
    - China, 1950-1951 (Box 84, Folder 864)
    - Civil Defense
      - local, 1950-1951 (Box 84, Folder 865)
      - national, 1950-1951 (Box 84, Folder 866)
      - general, 1950-1951 (Box 84, Folder 867)
      - state, 1950-1951 (Box 84, Folder 868)
    - Cleveland Health Museum, 1950-1951 (Box 84, Folder 869)
    - Connecticut Health League, 1950-1951 (Box 84, Folder 870-871)
    - Committee on Careers in Nursing, 1950-1951 (Box 84, Folder 872)
    - Connecticut Nutrition Council, 1950-1951 (Box 84, Folder 873)
    - Connecticut Trudeau Society, 1950-1951 (Box 84, Folder 874)
    - Dental Clinic Society of New Haven, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 875)
    - General D, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 876)
    - Sir Allen Daley, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 877)
    - General E, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 878)
    - General F, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 879)
    - Fellowships, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 880)
    - General G, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 881)
    - General H, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 882-883)
    - Health Officers (full time) Conference, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 884)
    - Health Councils, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 885)
    - General I, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 886)
    - General J, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 887)
    - General K, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 888)
    - General L, 1950-1951 (Box 85, Folder 889)
    - General M, 1950-1951 (Box 86, Folder 890)
    - Medical School, Dean of, 1934-1951 (Box 86, Folder 891)
    - General N, 1950-1951 (Box 86, Folder 892-893)
    - National Security Resources Board, 1950-1951 (Box 86, Folder 894)
    - Navy, U.S., 1950-1951 (Box 86, Folder 895)
    - New Canaan, 1950-1951 (Box 86, Folder 896)
    - General O, 1950-1951 (Box 86, Folder 897)
    - General P, 1950-1951 (Box 86, Folder 898)
    - General R, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 899)
    - General S, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 900)
    - Society of Public Health Educators, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 901)
    - General T, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 902)
    - General U, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 903)
    - General V, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 904)
    - General W, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 905)
    - General Y, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 906)
    - Yale Chapter of Sigma XI, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 907)
    - Yale Committee on Statistics, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 908)
    - Yale Department of Architecture, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 909-910)
    - Yale Medical Society, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 911)
    - Yale Office of Veterans Affairs, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 912)
    - Yale Service Bureau, 1950-1951 (Box 87, Folder 913)
    - G.R. Cowgill - Nutrition, 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 914)
    - G.H. Dession - Law, 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 915)
    - J.R. Paul - Preventive Medicine, 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 916)
    - R.H. Suttie - Sanitary Engineering, 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 917)
    - Occupational Medicine and Industrial Hygiene, 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 918-919)
    - P.B. Cowles - Bacteriology, 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 920)
    - Medical Care, 1951 (Box 88, Folder 921)
    - Committee of Physicians for the Improvement of Medical Care, Inc., 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 922)
    - Sanitation of the Environment, 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 923)
    - C.C. Wilson - School Health, 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 924)
    - Lovic P. Herrington, 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 925-926)
    - Clement C. Clay, 1950-1951 (Box 88, Folder 927)
    - Eleanor M. King, 1950-1951 (Box 89, Folder 932)
    - Abraham Gelperin, 1948-1951 (Box 89, Folder 933-934)
    - Barbara Johnson, 1950-1951 (Box 89, Folder 935)
    - Richard Ford, 1950-1951 (Box 89, Folder 936)
    - Milton I. Roemer, 1949-1951 (Box 89, Folder 937-939)
    - Milton I. Roemer, 1949-1950 (Box 90, Folder 940-941)
    - Robert M. Brown, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 942)
    - Joseph E. Reese, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 943)
    - George S. Buis, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 944)
    - George James, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 945)
    - Percy Stocks, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 946)
    - Howard Stuart Pfirman, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 947)
    - Hilda Bertha Kroeger, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 948)
    - Nelson Foss Evans, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 949)
    - Dorothy Rosenstock Granoff, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 951)
    - Kenneth Earl Markuson, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 952)
    - Laurence Reginald Wyatt, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 953)
    - Muriel Ann Wyatt, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 954)
    - Irene Gilbert Hiscock, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 955)
    - Harry Auerbach, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 956)
    - Staff Meetings, General File, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 957-958)
    - Staff Meetings, General File, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 959)
    - Housing, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 960)
    - Nursing, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 961)
    - Chronic disease, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 962)
    - Leprosy, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 963)
    - President's office, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 964)
    - Director of Medical Affairs, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 965)
    - Provost's office, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 966)
    - Treasurer's office, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 967)
    - Budget, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 968)
    - Recommendations for appointment, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 969)
    - Dean - Graduate School, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 970)
    - Assistant Dean - Graduate School, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 971)
    - Registrar - Graduate School, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 972)
    - Dean - Medical School, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 973)
    - Assistant Dean - Medical School, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 974)
    - Executive Secretary - Medical School, 1950-1951 (Box 91, Folder 975)
    - Committee on Admissions - Medical School, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 976)
    - Stanley H. Davis - Business Office, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 977)
    - Registrar - Medical School, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 978)
    - School of Nursing, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 979)
    - University Library, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 980)
    - Medical School Library, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 981)
    - Historical Library, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 982)
    - Delta Omega, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 983)
    - Board of Permanent Officers, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 984-985)
    - Board of Permanent Officers - Sheffield Scientific School, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 986)
    - Department of University Health, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 987)
    - Swimming Pool study - Gift: Wallace and Tiernan, 1949-1951 (Box 92, Folder 988)
    - Candidates for jobs, 1950-1951 (Box 92, Folder 989)
    - Accreditation Plan, 1950-1951 (Box 93, Folder 990)
    - Department of Psychiatry and Mental Hygiene, 1950-1951 (Box 93, Folder 991)
    - Bishop Museum Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 93, Folder 992)
    - Rehabilitation Study Unit, 1950-1951 (Box 93, Folder 993)
    - Public Health Department - General, 1950-1951 (Box 93, Folder 994)
    - Committee on the Administration Department, 1950-1951 (Box 93, Folder 995)
    - Newsletter, 1950-1951 (Box 93, Folder 996)
    - Publishers, 1950-1951 (Box 93, Folder 997-998)
    - Requests for candidates for jobs, 1950-1951 (Box 93, Folder 999-1000)
    - Visiting lecturers, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1001)
    - Field trips, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1002)
    - Annual reports, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1003)
    - Winslow Number, Yale Journal of Biology and Medicine, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1004)
    - Legislation and Federal Bills, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1005)
    - Recommendations for jobs, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1006)
    - Vital statistics, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1007)
    - Secretarial staff, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1008)
    - Contributions, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1009)
    - Survey - Columbus, OH, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1010)
    - Survey - Boston, MA, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1011)
    - Ladies Aid, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1012)
    - New Haven Army Advisory Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1013)
    - Ira V. Hiscock - Rotary, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1014)
    - Governor, State of Connecticut, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1015)
    - Connecticut Heart Association, 1950-1951 (Box 94, Folder 1016)
    - Connecticut Heart Association, 1950-1951 (Box 95, Folder 1017)
    - New Haven Heart Association, 1950-1951 (Box 95, Folder 1018)
    - American Dental Association, 1950-1951 (Box 95, Folder 1019)
    - American Epidemiological Society, 1950-1951 (Box 95, Folder 1020)
    - American Medical Association, 1950-1951 (Box 95, Folder 1021-1022)
    - American Public Health Association, 1950-1951 (Box 95, Folder 1023-1024)
    - American Public Health Association, 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 1025)
    - American Journal of Public Health, 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 1026)
    - American Public Health Association
      - Committee on Motion Pictures, 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 1027)
      - Committee on State Health Studies, 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 1028)
      - Committee on Professional Education, 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 1029)
      - Committee on Administrative Practices, 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 1030)
      - Annual Meeting, 1950 (Box 96, Folder 1031)
    - Connecticut Public Health Association, 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 1032)
    - American Public Health Association
      - Sanitation Project, 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 1033-1034)
      - Committee on Administrative Practice, Subcommittee on Medical Care, 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 1035)
      - Subcommittee on Mental Hygiene, 1950-1951 (Box 96, Folder 1036)
    - Evaluation schedules, 1950-1951 (Box 97, Folder 1037)
    - American Public Health Association - Committee on Health Education, 1950-1951 (Box 97, Folder 1038)
    - American Red Cross - National, 1950-1951 (Box 97, Folder 1039)
    - American Red Cross - New Haven Chapter, 1950-1951 (Box 97, Folder 1040)
    - American Social Hygiene Association, 1950-1951 (Box 97, Folder 1041)
    - American Heart Association, 1950-1951 (Box 97, Folder 1042-1043)
    - American Heart Association, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 1044)
    - Association of Schools of Public Health, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 1045)
    - California UCLA, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 1046-1047)
    - Columbia, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 1048)
    - Harvard, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 1049)
    - Hopkins, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 1050)
    - Michigan, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 1051)
    - Minnesota, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 1052)
    - North Carolina, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 1053)
    - Pittsburgh, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 1054)
    - Boy Scouts of America, 1950-1951 (Box 99, Folder 1055-1056)
    - Connecticut Cancer Society, 1950-1951 (Box 99, Folder 1058)
    - Connecticut Cancer Society - Survey, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 1059)
    - Connecticut Cancer Bulletin, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 1060)
    - Connecticut Hospital Association, 1950-1951 (Box 99, Folder 1061)
    - Connecticut Diabetes Association, 1950-1951 (Box 99, Folder 1062)
    - Connecticut Society for Mental Hygiene, 1950-1951 (Box 99, Folder 1063)
    - New Haven Mental Hygiene Society, 1950-1951 (Box 99, Folder 1064)
    - Connecticut State Department of Health, 1950-1951 (Box 99, Folder 1065)
    - State of Connecticut Water Commission, 1950-1951 (Box 99, Folder 1066)
    - Commissioner of Health, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1067)
    - Preventable of Health, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1068)
    - Vital statistics, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1069)
    - Mental hygiene, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1070)
    - Venereal disease, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1071)
    - Tuberculosis Commission, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1072)
    - Connecticut State Department of Education, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1073)
    - State of Connecticut Commission on Alcoholism, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1074)
    - Connecticut State Department of Finance and Control, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1075)
    - Connecticut State Medical Society, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1076)
    - Hawaii, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1077-1079)
    - Institute of Inter-American Affairs, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 1080)
    - National Association of Housing Officials, 1950-1951 (Box 101, Folder 1084)
    - National Committee for Mental Hygiene, 1950-1951 (Box 101, Folder 1085)
    - National Association for Mental Hygiene, 1950-1951 (Box 101, Folder 1086)
    - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, 1950-1951 (Box 101, Folder 1087-1088)
    - New Haven Chapter, N.F.I.P., 1950-1951 (Box 101, Folder 1089)
    - National Health Council, 1950-1951 (Box 101, Folder 1090-1091)
    - National Health Council, 1950-1951 (Box 102, Folder 1092-1093)
    - National Social Welfare Assembly, 1950-1951 (Box 102, Folder 1094-1095)
    - National Publicity Council, 1950-1951 (Box 102, Folder 1096)
    - National Emergency Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 102, Folder 1097)
    - National Organization for Public Health Nursing, 1950-1951 (Box 102, Folder 1098)
    - Connecticut Public Health Nursing Association, 1950-1951 (Box 102, Folder 1099)
    - National Research Council, 1950-1951 (Box 103, Folder 1100)
    - National Sanitation Foundation, 1950-1951 (Box 103, Folder 1101)
    - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness, 1950-1951 (Box 103, Folder 1102-1105)
    - National Tuberculosis Association, 1950-1951 (Box 103, Folder 1106)
    - Connecticut Tuberculosis Association, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1107)
    - New Haven Tuberculosis Association, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1108)
    - New Haven Board of Health, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1109)
    - Board of Health, Minutes of meetings, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1110)
    - Rheumatic Fever and Cardiac Program, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1111)
    - New Haven Council of Social Agencies, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1113)
    - New Haven Hospital, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1114)
    - New Haven Department of Education, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 1116)
    - Visiting Nurse Association of New Haven, 1950-1951 (Box 105, Folder 1117)
    - Society of American Bacteriologists, 1950-1951 (Box 105, Folder 1119)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1950-1951 (Box 105, Folder 1120)
    - United States Army, 1950-1951 (Box 105, Folder 1121-1124)
    - Department of the Air Force, 1950-1951 (Box 105, Folder 1125)
    - U.S. Public Health Service, 1950-1951 (Box 106, Folder 1126-1128)
    - Venereal Disease Study, 1950-1951 (Box 106, Folder 1129)
    - Mental hygiene, 1950-1951 (Box 106, Folder 1130)
    - Cancer Control Curriculum, 1950-1951 (Box 106, Folder 1131)
    - Grant RG - 1487 (c) Okey U.S. Public Health Service, 1950-1951 (Box 106, Folder 1132)
    - National Institutes of Health, 1950-1951 (Box 106, Folder 1133)
    - U.S.P.H.S.-Division of Chronic Disease, 1950-1951 (Box 106, Folder 1134)
    - Bureau of State Services, 1950-1951 (Box 106, Folder 1135)
    - Division of International Health, 1950-1951 (Box 107, Folder 1136)
    - Health Departments (City, County, State), 1950-1951 (Box 107, Folder 1137-1139)
    - New York City Health Departments, 1950-1951 (Box 107, Folder 1140)
    - Mississippi State Board of Health, 1951 (Box 107, Folder 1141)
    - Y.M.C.A. - Y.W.C.A., 1950-1951 (Box 107, Folder 1142)
    - Community Chests and Councils, 1950-1951 (Box 107, Folder 1143)
    - Community Chests and Councils, 1950-1951 (Box 108, Folder 1144-1146)
    - National Budget Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 108, Folder 1147)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1950-1951 (Box 108, Folder 1148)
    - University of Massachusetts, 1950-1951 (Box 108, Folder 1149)
    - World Health Organization, 1950-1951 (Box 108, Folder 1150)
  - 1951-1952
    - A General, 1951-1952 (Box 109, Folder 1151-1153)
    - C General, 1951-1952 (Box 109, Folder 1154-1156)
    - American Cancer Society, 1951-1952 (Box 109, Folder 1157)
    - Association for Retarded Children in Greater New Haven, 1951-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1158)
    - B General, 1951-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1159)
    - A.S. Barnes Company, 1951-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1160)
    - China, 1951-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1161-1162)
    - Civil Defense - local, 1951-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1163)
    - Civil Defense - state, 1951-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1164)
    - Civil Defense - national, 1951-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1165)
    - Civil Defense - general, 1951-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1166)
    - Cleveland Health Museum, 1951-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1167)
    - Committee on Careers in Nursing, 1951-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1168)
    - Connecticut Health League, 1951-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1169)
    - Connecticut Nutrition Council, 1951-1952 (Box 110, Folder 1170)
    - Connecticut Trudeau Society, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1171)
    - D General, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1172)
    - Sir Allen Daley, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1173)
    - Dental Clinic Society of New Haven, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1174)
    - Denver Survey, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1175-1176)
    - E General, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1177)
    - F General, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1178)
    - Fellowships, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1179)
    - G General, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1180)
    - Group Health of Greater New Haven, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1181)
    - H General, 1951-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1182)
    - Health Information Foundation, 1951-1952 (Box 112, Folder 1183-1186)
    - Health Insurance Plan of Greater New York, 1951-1952 (Box 112, Folder 1187)
    - Health Officers (full time) Conference, 1951-1952 (Box 112, Folder 1188)
    - Human Relations Area Files, Inc., 1951-1952 (Box 112, Folder 1189)
    - I General, 1951-1952 (Box 112, Folder 1190)
    - J General, 1951-1952 (Box 113, Folder 1191)
    - K General, 1951-1952 (Box 113, Folder 1192)
    - L General, 1951-1952 (Box 113, Folder 1193)
    - M General, 1951-1952 (Box 113, Folder 1194-1195)
    - Community Welfare Council of Milwaukee County, 1951-1952 (Box 113, Folder 1196)
    - N General, 1951-1952 (Box 113, Folder 1197-1198)
    - New Canaan, 1951-1952 (Box 114, Folder 1199)
    - New England Public Health Institute, 1952 (Box 114, Folder 1200)
    - New Haven Health Council, 1952 (Box 114, Folder 1201)
    - O General, 1951-1952 (Box 114, Folder 1202)
    - P General, 1951-1952 (Box 114, Folder 1203)
    - President's Commission on the Health Needs of the Nation, 1952 (Box 114, Folder 1204)
    - Q General (void), 1951-1952 (Box 114, Folder 1205)
    - R General, 1951-1952 (Box 114, Folder 1206)
    - S General, 1951-1952 (Box 114, Folder 1207)
    - Society of Public Health Educators, 1951-1952 (Box 114, Folder 1208)
    - Surveys: list of surveys filed in Dr. Hiscock's office, 1951-1952 (Box 114, Folder 1209)
    - T General, 1952-1953 (Box 114, Folder 1210)
    - U General, 1951-1952 (Box 114, Folder 1211-1212)
    - U General, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1213)
    - V General, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1214)
    - Visitors, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1215)
    - W General, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1216)
    - Wisconsin Anti-Tuberculosis Association, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1217)
    - X General (void), 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1218)
    - Y General, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1219)
    - Yale Chapter of Sigma XI, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1220)
    - Yale Department of Architecture, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1221)
    - Yale Medical Society, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1222)
    - Yale New Bureau, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1223)
    - Yale Office of Veterans Affairs, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1224)
    - Z General, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1225)
    - G.R. Cowgill - Nutrition, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1226)
    - G.H. Dession: Law, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1227)
    - J.R. Paul: Preventive Medicine, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1228)
    - R.H. Suttie: Sanitary Engineering, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1229)
    - Occupational Medicine and Industrial Hygiene, 1951-1952 (Box 115, Folder 1230-1231)
    - Occupational Medicine and Industrial Hygiene, 1951-1952 (Box 116, Folder 1232)
    - P.B. Cowles - Bacteriology, 1951-1952 (Box 116, Folder 1233)
    - Medical care, 1952 (Box 116, Folder 1234)